chromefans.org 2017-12-01

# Privacy Policy - Google Chrome Fans

You are here: [Home](http://www.chromefans.org/ "ChromeFans Home") > [About](http://www.chromefans.org/about/)

Below is information regarding ChromeFans.org commitment to protect the privacy of users and to ensure the integrity of the Internet.

  * Internet user privacy is of paramount importance to ChromeFans. The success of our business depends upon our ability to maintain the trust of our users. If for any reason you have concerns about our website's privacy policies, please contact me. I'm committed to ensuring that every user's needs are addressed.
  * In the course of delivering this site to you, ChromeFans does NOT collect any personally-identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number or email address from users of this web site without your knowledge, and are taking measures to protect your privacy. 
  * You can send email requesting help and your email will NOT be shared in any way with any third party(ies), and will only be used to send replies to you. 
  * **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, ChromeFans.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

  * **Cookies and Web Beacons**

ChromeFans.org does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ChromeFans.org send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

ChromeFans.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. ChromeFans.org's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

  * **Search history and cookies**

The search feature of ChromeFans.org is based Google Custom Search. More information, please visit [Google Privacy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/).

  * **Open SEO Stats extension privacy policy**

Chromefans.org provides this Privacy Policy to inform users who download Open SEO Stats extension("Extension") from Google Chrome Store. The Extension may include links or otherwise allow you to access and perhaps submit information to third-party applications or sites(For example: Google, Bing or Alexa). This Privacy Policy applies to the Extension only. 

You are not required to register with us to download the Extension, and may do so anonymously.

The Extension does not collect any personal information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.). Further, it does not collect or report back to us (or anyone else) any data regarding your computer keystrokes or other data unrelated to the services the Extension provides.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this matter, please feel free to contact me.

  * Next article: [I am on Google+, Add me in your circle to see updates](http://www.chromefans.org/about/google-plus.htm)
